bananalotto.co.uk 2013-04-26

# Bananalotto - 100% Free Game - Win: Vouchers, prizes, DVD, mobiles, video games, holidays, Nintendo DS, PSP, digital camera, PS3, MP3 players !

### Purpose of this Privacy Policy

Mediastay Ltd is registered with The Information Commissioner's Office under the Data Protection Act 1998 (ICO Registration No. Z962923X).   
This Privacy Policy relates to the BANANALOTTO website accessible at [www.bananalotto.co.uk](http://www.bananalotto.co.uk/) (the "Website") which is owned by and operated by the proprietor : Mediastay Limited C/O SPAIN BROTHERS & CO 29 Manor Road Folkestone, Kent CT20 2SE ENGLAND ("Mediastay"). Company Registration No. 5958600.

Mediastay respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. Mediastay also has obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998 regarding the collection, use and storage of personal information relating to individuals which Mediastay receives via the Website. Mediastay provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of Mediastay's policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. Mediastay have structured the Website so that, if you are simply visiting the Website and not playing Bananalotto, you can do so without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information.

Mediastay ensures that any data about individuals received via the Site will be processed in accordance with the eight principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Act") and the policy set out below.

### Data Collection and Purpose Specification

The types of personal data you may provide to us via the Website may include name, address, phone, e-mail address, User IDs and passwords, contact preferences and other similar information.

Mediastay collects your personal data in order to organise, administer and run a free game with prizes called "Bananalotto" which is accessible via the Website. More specifically, Mediastay uses your information to communicate with you via e-mail and otherwise regarding your entry into such games of Bananalotto and to update you on winning games and prizes. 

Mediastay may also from time to time use your personal data to inform you of special games being organised by Mediastay or other services and benefits Mediastay may offer. Mediastay may also use your personal data to gain a better understanding regarding who uses Bananalotto Website and how they use it, including the web pages they access so as to be able to improve the Website. 

Occasionally, Mediastay may also use your information to contact you for market research regarding Mediastay's products and services. Mediastay will give you the opportunity to opt-out of market research and customers surveys.

By providing your personal data via the Website you consent to such use of your personal data.

### Disclosure to Third Parties

Unless Mediastay has your consent including that given below, Mediastay will not disclose your personal data to third party organisations, institutions and authorities unless required by law and Mediastay will not sell, rent or lease your personal data to others.

Sometimes Mediastay may need to give information to agents and sub-contractors for the purpose of administering your participation in Bananalotto. In these circumstances, Mediastay always ensure that the information is safe and secure.

Mediastay may also transfer your personal data to certain selected third party partner service providers with whom Mediastay have a commercial relationship so that they can inform you of offers which you may be interested in. Unless you indicate otherwise, your consent to such use and transfer of your personal data is given to us for this. You may indicate your refusal to authorize the publication of personal information to third parties in this way by simply ticking the "No" check box on the registration form following the text: "I'd like to receive great offers from our partners (competitions, great ideas, great prizes...)" when you register with Bananalotto and provide personal data. If you have previously expressed a desire to receive offers from partners of Mediastay, you may also remove such consent at any time in the "My Account" section, available on the Bananalotto homepage or by clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link in each promotional e-mail received. You agree that if Mediastay transfers ownership or management of the Website to a third party Mediastay may also transfer your personal data to such third party, provided such third party agrees to observe this Privacy Policy.

Mediastay does not collect extra information about its visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 

If Mediastay wishes to use your personal data for a new purpose, other than for which it was originally supplied, Mediastay will ask you first. Mediastay takes seriously the trust you place in us. 

### Links to Third Party Websites

Parts of the Website may contain links to third party websites for your convenience and information. If you use these links, you will leave the Website. When you access a third party website, please understand that Mediastay does not control the content and is not responsible for the privacy practices of that site. Mediastay suggests that you carefully review the privacy policies of each website you visit. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those third party websites linked to the Website. These other websites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. 

### Security

Mediastay does not give visitors to Bananalotto Website the option of using a secure transmission method to send Mediastay their personal data, unless otherwise indicated. Accordingly, your attention is drawn to the fact that any information carried over the Internet is _not_ secure. Information can be intercepted, lost, redirected, changed and read by third parties.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain accuracy, and ensure proper use of information, Mediastay has employed physical, electronic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure the information Mediastay collects online.

All Mediastay's employees and data processors who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of such personal data.

### Your Rights to Access Personal Data

You have rights in relation to your personal data held by Mediastay under the Act, including a right to have it modified and to request access to it. For any enquiry or concern about your personal data, or to request access to your personal data please contact Mediastay's Data Compliance Officer as set out below: 

Data Compliance Officer :  
**MEDIASTAY Limited**  
C/O SPAIN BROTHERS & CO   
29 Manor Road   
Folkestone, Kent  
CT20 2SE   
ENGLAND   
****

Requests may also be made directly on the Website in the "My Account" section, accessible from the homepage. Mediastay must provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which it holds about you within 40 days of receiving your written request. The Act allows us to charge a fee of £10 pounds for this service. Evidence or proof of your identity (for example, a passport, driver's licence or current bills) will be required.

It is in Mediastay's and your interest that Mediastay holds accurate data about you. If you believe the personal data Mediastay holds about you is inaccurate in any way please contact us on the above address. 

Where appropriate, you may have your personal data: 

  * Erased;
  * corrected, rectified, amended or updated;
  * clarified or completed.

If you have authorised Mediastay to use your personal data, you may cancel that authorisation at any time by writing to the address above. Mediastay will stop using your personal data within three days after receiving the letter.

Mediastay reserves the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal and allow you to challenge our decision.

### Complaints and Disputes

Medistay is committed to working with you to obtain a fair and rapid resolution of any complaints or disputes relating to privacy matters. Please send us your questions and comments regarding our privacy practices to the address set out above.           

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

If there are changes or additions to the terms of this Privacy Policy, Mediastay will post those changes on the Website so that you will always know what information Mediastay collects online, how it is used, and what choices you have. Mediastay, therefore, recommends that you regularly check this Privacy Policy page for updates. Regardless of any changes Mediastay makes to this Privacy Policy, Mediastay will always use your personal data in accordance with the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information, unless you give your express consent for Mediastay to do otherwise.
